export const steppingStonesQuiz = [
        {
          question: "What is hygiene?  The things we do to ______________.",
          options: [
            "Eat healthy and have good nutrition",
            "Keep our body clean and healthy every day",
            "Keep our body dirty and unhealthy every day",
            "Get a good amount of sleep each night"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 1 
        },
        {
          question: "You and your friends play outside in the sun and sweat a lot. Should you wear the same clothes the next day?",
          options: ["Yes", "No"],
          correctAnswer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "What should you be doing along with brushing your teeth?",
          options: [
            "Eating breakfast",
            "Going back to bed",
            "Taking a shower",
            "Flossing your teeth"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 3
        },
        {
          question: "What should you always do before a meal or after going to the bathroom?",
          options: [
            "Brush your teeth",
            "Wash your hands",
            "Take a shower",
            "Say please and thank you"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "If you can't see any dirt on your hands, are they clean?",
          options: ["Yes", "No"],
          correctAnswer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "What causes cavities to form in your teeth?",
          options: [
            "Too much plaque on your teeth",
            "Eating hard foods",
            "Brushing your teeth too hard",
            "Not showering often"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "What is the most important meal of the day?",
          options: [
            "Breakfast",
            "Lunch",
            "Afternoon snack",
            "Dinner"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "Why is proper nutrition important?",
          options: [
            "Proper nutrition makes your food tastier",
            "Proper nutrition provides you energy to learn and play",
            "Proper nutrition makes you never get sick"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "You go to the school cafeteria for lunch. Which option would you pick for the healthiest meal?",
          options: [
            "Pizza and fries",
            "Chicken nuggets and corn",
            "Peanut butter and jelly and chips",
            "Grilled chicken and carrots"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 3
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is NOT a large source of protein you could include in your diet?",
          options: [
            "Chicken",
            "Beans",
            "Broccoli",
            "Tofu"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 2
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is the most healthiest balanced plate of food?",
          options: [
            "1/2 fruits and vegetables, 1/4 protein, 1/4 carbohydrates",
            "1/4 fruits and vegetables, 1/4 protein, 1/2 carbohydrates",
            "1/4 fruits and vegetables, 1/2 protein, 1/4 carbohydrates"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "You should never eat any unhealthy snacks or foods, even if you like them.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "Using technology before sleeping doesn't make it harder to fall asleep.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "Sleep can give your body the strength to fight off sickness.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "Doing which of the following can help you fall asleep?",
          options: [
            "Watch television",
            "Check your phone",
            "Focus on breathing",
            "Eat candy"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 2
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following could happen if you don't get enough sleep?",
          options: [
            "You could have trouble waking up on time",
            "You could have trouble paying attention in class",
            "You could feel sick or have a headache",
            "All of the above"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 3
        },
        {
          question: "Getting enough sleep can help with performance in sports and in school.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "You are getting ready to go to sleep. Which of the following will make it harder to fall asleep?",
          options: [
            "Looking at your phone or other technology",
            "Brushing your teeth",
            "Showering",
            "Saying goodnight to your family"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "Before hugging or touching someone, it is important to ask for permission first.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "When someone does not want you to touch them, you have to respect their decision.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "You get a low score on a test and feel embarrassed. Which of the following is the healthiest response?",
          options: [
            "Tell yourself you are bad at school",
            "Remain confident in yourself and keep working hard",
            "Complain about the test to your peers",
            "Stop studying for that class"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "Your classmate, Ishan, gets a question wrong and feels embarrassed. Another classmate, Taylor, begins making fun of them. Which of the following is the healthiest response?",
          options: [
            "Join Taylor in making fun of Ishan",
            "Ignore what's going on",
            "Tell Taylor it's not nice to make fun of others",
            "Shout out the correct answer"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 2
        },
        {
          question: "Your friend, Emmanuel, seems really worried about something. Which of the following is the healthiest response?",
          options: [
            "Offer to help Emmanuel if he is comfortable sharing",
            "Ignore the situation",
            "Tell Emmanuel to get over it",
            "Continue asking him until he tells you what he is worried about"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 0
        },
        {
          question: "If you have concerns about your safety, who is the best person to speak to?",
          options: [
            "Friend",
            "Sibling",
            "Teammate",
            "Adult"
          ],
          correctAnswer: 3
        }
      ];